<resources>
    <string name="app_name"></string>
    <string name="test">testing!!</string>
    <string name="about_page">
    Welcome to cookeasi!
    Not everyone is a chef, looking at a fridge and deducing recipes is not a skill most people have.
        Hence, cookeasi. The app which conveniently takes items from your fridge and displays all the recipes possible with them.
        Cookeasi aims to save any unnecessary shopping, orders to restaurants, and even expand the horizons of ones own cooking journey.
    </string>
    <string name="recipe_example">
egg
Salt
Butter
<p>
    Instructions:<br />

Crack two eggs into a bowl and beat them with a fork.<br />
Season the eggs with a pinch of salt and pepper.<br />
Heat a small non-stick pan over medium heat.<br />
Add a small knob of butter or a drizzle of oil to the pan.<br />
Once the butter has melted or the oil is hot, pour in the beaten eggs.<br />
Use a spatula to stir the eggs gently as they cook, until they are scrambled to your liking.<br />
Serve hot and enjoy! </p> </string>

    <string name="avocado_toast">
        toast<br />
avocado<br />
salt<br />
pepper<br />
red pepper flakes<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Toast 2 slices of whole grain bread to your desired level of doneness.<br />
  2. Cut an avocado in half, remove the pit and mash the flesh with a fork.<br />
  3. Spread the mashed avocado onto the toasted bread.<br />
  4. Sprinkle salt, pepper, and red pepper flakes on top of the avocado toast.<br />
  5. Serve immediately and enjoy!
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="yogurt_parfait">
        greek yogurt<br />
        fresh or frozen berries<br />
        granola<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Take a jar or a bowl.<br />
  2. Add a layer of Greek yogurt at the bottom.<br />
  3. Add a layer of fresh or frozen berries of your choice on top of the yogurt.<br />
  4. Repeat the layering of yogurt and berries until the jar is full.<br />
  5. Sprinkle granola on top of the final layer of yogurt.<br />
  6. Serve immediately and enjoy!
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="peanut_butter_banana_smoothie">
        frozen banana<br />
        almond milk<br />
        peanut butter<br />
        honey<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Cut a frozen banana into small pieces.<br />
  2. Add the frozen banana pieces, 1/2 cup of almond milk, 1 tablespoon of peanut butter, and 1 tablespoon of honey to a blender.<br />
  3. Blend all the ingredients until smooth.<br />
  4. Pour the smoothie into a glass and serve immediately.<br />
  5. Enjoy your delicious and healthy smoothie!
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="grilled_chicken_salad">
        chicken breast<br />
        salt<br />
        pepper<br />
        lettuce<br />
        tomatoes<br />
        cucumbers<br />
        vinaigrette dressing<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Preheat a grill to medium-high heat.<br />
  2. Season 4 chicken breast with salt, pepper, and your favorite spices.<br />
  3. Place the chicken breasts on the grill and cook for 6 to 7 minutes on each side, or until the internal temperature reaches 165°F.<br />
  4. Remove the chicken from the grill and let it cool for a few minutes.<br />
  5. Chop the grilled chicken into bite-sized pieces.<br />
  6. In a large bowl, mix together your lettuce, tomatoes, cucumbers, and a vinaigrette dressing.<br />
  7. Add the chopped chicken to the salad and mix everything together.<br />
  8. Serve immediately and enjoy!
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="veggie_wrap">
        whole grain wrap<br />
        hummus<br />
        vegetables<br />
        cheese<br />
        lettuce<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Warm a whole grain wrap in the microwave or on a pan.<br />
  2. Spread 2 tablespoons of hummus on the wrap.<br />
  3. Add your favorite roasted vegetables on top of the hummus.<br />
  4. Sprinkle 1/4 cup of grated cheese on top of the vegetables.<br />
  5. Add a handful of lettuce on top of the cheese.<br />
  6. Roll the wrap tightly and slice it in half.<br />
  7. Serve immediately and enjoy your delicious veggie wrap!
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="lentil_soup">
        olive oil<br />
        onion<br />
        carrots<br />
        celery<br />
        dried lentils<br />
        vegetable broth<br />
        tomatoes<br />
        cumin<br />
        paprika<br />
        salt<br />
        pepper<br />
        <p>
    Instructions:<br />
    1. Heat 1 tablespoon of olive oil in a large pot over medium heat.<br />
    2. Add 1 diced onion, 2 chopped carrots, and 2 chopped celery stalks to the pot.<br />
    3. Cook for 5 to 7 minutes, or until the vegetables are tender.<br />
    4. Add 1 cup of dried lentils, 4 cups of vegetable broth, 1 can of diced tomatoes, 1 teaspoon of cumin, and 1 teaspoon of paprika to the pot.<br />
    5. Bring the soup to a boil, then reduce the heat and simmer for 20 to 25 minutes, or until the lentils are tender.<br />
    6. Season the soup with salt and pepper to taste.<br />
    7. Serve the soup hot and enjoy!
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="baked_salmon">
        salmon<br />
        salt<br />
        pepper<br />
        honey<br />
        soy sauce<br />
        minced garlic<br />
        minced ginger<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Preheat the oven to 375°F.<br />
  2. Season 4 salmon fillets with salt, pepper, and your favorite herbs and spices.<br />
  3. Place the salmon fillets in a baking dish.<br />
  4. Bake the salmon for 12 to 15 minutes, or until the internal temperature reaches 145°F.<br />
  5. In a small bowl, mix together 2 tablespoons of honey, 2 tablespoons of soy sauce, 1 tablespoon of minced garlic, and 1 tablespoon of minced ginger.<br />
  6. Brush the honey glaze on top of the baked salmon.<br />
  7. Serve the salmon hot and enjoy!<br />
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="spaghetti_bolognese">
        spaghetti<br />
        olive oil<br />
        onions<br />
        carrots<br />
        celery<br />
        ground beef<br />
        can of crushed tomatoes<br />
        dried basil<br />
        dried oregano<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Cook 8 ounces of spaghetti according to the package instructions.<br />
  2. Heat 1 tablespoon of olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br />
  3. Add 1 diced onion, 2 chopped carrots, and 2 chopped celery stalks to the skillet.<br />
  4. Cook for 5 to 7 minutes, or until the vegetables are tender.<br />
  5. Add 1 pound of ground beef to the skillet and cook until browned.<br />
  6. Add 1 can of crushed tomatoes, 1 teaspoon of dried basil, and 1 teaspoon of dried oregano to the skillet.<br />
  7. Reduce the heat and let the sauce simmer for 15 to 20 minutes.<br />
  8. Serve the spaghetti with the bolognese sauce on top.<br />
  9. Enjoy your delicious spaghetti bolognese!<br />
</p>
    </string>

    <string name="quinoa_and_black_bean">
        quinoa<br />
        black beans<br />
        red bell peppers<br />
        green bell pepper<br />
        avocado<br />
        cilantro<br />
        olive oil<br />
        lime juice<br />
        cumin<br />
        chili powder<br />
        <p>
  Instructions:<br />
  1. Cook 1 cup of quinoa according to the package instructions.<br />
  2. In a large bowl, mix together 1 can of black beans, 1 diced red bell pepper, 1 diced green bell pepper, 1 diced avocado, and 1/4 cup of chopped cilantro.<br />
  3. Add the cooked quinoa to the bowl and mix everything together.<br />
  4. In a small bowl, mix together 1 tablespoon of olive oil, 1 tablespoon of lime juice, 1 teaspoon of cumin, and 1 teaspoon of chili powder.<br />
  5. Pour the dressing on top of the quinoa and black bean bowl.<br />
  6. Serve the bowl hot or cold and enjoy!
</p>
    </string>
</resources>